titanium-software.fr 2017-06-01

# Titanium Software - Home

* * *

**DISCLAIMER**

Titanium Software provides software and information on the use of this software for users. Our goal is to keep this information timely and accurate. If errors are brought to our attention, we will try to correct them. However, Titanium Software accepts no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to the information on this site.

The information on this website is

• of a general nature only and is not intended to address the specific circumstances of any particular individual or entity;  
• not necessarily comprehensive, complete, accurate, or up-to-date; and  
• not professional advice.

It is our goal to minimize disruption caused by technical errors. However, some information on our site may have been created or structured in files that are not error-free, and we cannot guarantee that our service will not be interrupted or otherwise affected by such problems. Titanium Software accepts no responsibility with regard to such problems incurred as a result of using this site or any linked external sites.

The software provided on this website contains a Software License Agreement which users must read and agree to follow as a condition of use. This Agreement contains information about the conditions by which the software is licensed and any limitations to the liability of Titanium Software.

**PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION**

This website does not automatically collect any information about visitors.

_**Email**_

Many webpages on the Titanium Software website contain a "Contact" button, which activates your email software and invites you to send your comments to a specific mailbox. We may keep some correspondence indefinitely. You may examine any information that we store about you by sending an email request. You may request that any email sent to Titanium Software (which is still in our possession) be deleted. Any disputes over Personal Data Collection issues will be handled by our Controller.

If you send personal email to Titanium Software, it is assumed that you wish to receive an email response unless you note otherwise. You will only be contacted regarding the content of your email and not for any other purpose.

_**Advertising and additional data collection**_  
Titanium Software does not set any cookies. Titanium Software does not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Titanium Software does not share any information about site visitors with other organizations or businesses for any purpose.

_**Links to external websites**_  
This website may link to external websites over which Titanium Software has no control and assumes no responsibility. Those websites may have different data protection policies than the Titanium Software website does, and users are encouraged to review the policies of these external sites upon visiting. Titanium Software does not receive any revenue from its links to external websites.

_**Personal Data Collection policy changes**_  
If the Personal Data Collection policy of this site changes, it will only affect data on visitors which is created after the date of a policy change. Any prior collected data will be governed under the Personal Data Collection policy in effect at the time the data was collected. Visitors will be alerted to any policy change through a revised data appearing at the bottom of this page.

_**Policy on users under the age of 13**_  
Titanium Software respects the privacy of children, and does not collect any personal information from children online, except as submitted in emails sent by the user. This site is not directed at children under 13 years of age and does not ask for age-identifying information from visitors. Any user under the age of 13 who contacts Titanium Software by email must have the consent or authorization of a parent or custodian to do so.

**SECURITY**

Titanium Software has appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that users have sent to Titanium Software through email.

**COPYRIGHT NOTICE**

This website, including all images and text, are Copyright © 2017 by Titanium Software. Reproduction, with or without alteration, is prohibited without prior written permission.

**CONTROLLER/WEBMASTER CONTACT INFORMATION**

The Controller and Webmaster, Joël Barrière, can be reached via email at [contact@titanium-software.fr](mailto:contact@titanium-software.fr)

Policy Last Updated: _March 19, 2017_
